Finding Aid for Athletic Department (University of Michigan) records, 1860-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sports Information Office, 1860-
  - Baseball
    - Photographs
      - Portraits and Action Photos
        - 2005 (headshots, game action, NCAA Regionals), contact sheets & digital files (CDs) (Box 227)
        - 2006 (headshots, game action), contact sheets & digital files (CDs) 1 volumes (Box 227)
        - 2007 (headshots, coach's families, NCAA Super Regionals, golf outing, baseball tailgate), contact sheets & digital files (CDs) 1 volumes (Box 227)
        - 2007 NCAA Super Regionals, video of Memphis and Vanderbilt games, 1 optical disks DVDs (Box 227)
        - 2008 (headshots, game action, NCAA Regionals, stadium construction shots, Wilpon dedication ceremony), 3 volumes contact sheets & digital files (CDs) (Box 228)
        - Support Staff Photos circa 1985-2005 (Box 228)
          (includes Jim Schneider, Ian Hume, Eric Keil, staff and student trainers, student managers, volunteer assistant coaches, including Alan Trammel during MLB strike in 1994-1995)
    - Season Statistics, Programs, etc.
      - Compiled Season Statistics 1936 1939-40, 1960-61, 1963-66, 1968-1997 (Box 195)
        (from media guides or other sources)
      - 1890, circa 1893, 1922-1923 (Box 195)
        (scorecards)
      - 1940/41 (Box 195)
      - 1960 (Box 195)
      - 1961 (Box 195)
      - 1962 (Box 195)
      - 1963 (Box 195)
      - 1964 (Box 195)
      - 1965 (Box 195)
      - 1966 (Box 195)
      - 1967 (Box 195)
      - 1968 (Box 195)
      - 1969 (Box 195)
      - 1970 (Box 195)
      - 1971 (Box 195)
      - 1972 (Box 195)
      - 1973 (Box 195)
      - 1974 (Box 195)
      - 1975 (Box 195)
      - 1976 (Box 195)
      - 1977 (Box 195)
      - 1978 (Box 195)
      - 1979 (Box 195)
      - 1980, 2 folders (Box 195)
      - 1981, 2 folders (Box 195)
      - 1982, 2 folders (Box 195)
      - 1983 (Box 195)
      - 1984 (Box 195)
      - 1985 (Box 195)
      - 1986 (Box 195)
      - 1987, 2 folders (Box 196)
      - 1988, 2 folders (Box 196)
      - 1989, 2 folders (Box 196)
      - 1990, 2 folders (Box 196)
      - 1991 (Box 196)
      - 1992, 2 folders (Box 196)
      - 1994, 2 folders (Box 196)
      - 1995 (Box 196)
      - 1996 Post Season Guides (Box 196)
      - 1996 Results and Statistics (Box 196)
      - 1997 Releases, 2 folders (Box 196)
      - 1997 Big Ten Tournament Results (Box 196)
      - 1999 Articles, 2 folders (Box 196)
      - 1999 Post Season Guides (Box 196)
      - 2001 Big Ten Tournament Guide (Box 196)
      - 2005 NCAA Regional Guide (Box 196)
      - 2008 Season Statistics (Box 226)
      - 2009 Media Relations Kit, 2 folders (Box 226)
    - Scorebooks
      - 1922, 1924-1928 (1929 Western and Japanese trip), 1930-1932, 1938, 1944-1960, 1962-1963, 1966-1967, 1972 (Box 93)
  - Basketball-men
    - Media Guides
      - 1933/34, 1937/38-1940/411947/48, 1949/50, 1957/58-1958/59 (Box 26-A)
      - 1961/62-1970/71 (Box 26-A)
      - 1963/64-1964/65, 1964 NCAA Tournament Press Books, 1965 Tournament Guide (Box 26-A)
      - 1970/71, 1971 NIT Tournament Guide (Box 26-A)
      - 1971/72-1976/77 (Box 26-A)
      - 1977/78-1980/81 (Box 26-A)
      - 1981/82-1983/84, 1984 NIT recap (Box 26-A)
      - 1984/85-1985/86, 1985, 1986 NCAA tournament guides (Box 26-A)
      - 1986/87-1987/88, 1987, 1988 NCAA tournament guides (Box 26-A)
      - 1988/89, 1989 NCAA Tournament Guide (Box 26-A)
      - 1989/90-1990/91, 1990 NCAA Tournament Guide (Box 26-B)
      - 1990/91, 1991 NCAA Tournament Guide (Box 26-B)
      - 1991/92, 1992 NCAA Tourney Guide and Press Book (Box 26-B)
      - 1992/93, 1993 NCAA Tournament Guides, 2 folders (Box 26-B)
      - 1993/94, 1994 NCAA Tournament Supplement and Guides, 2 folders (Box 26-B)
      - 1994/95, 1995 NCAA Tournament Guides (Box 26-B)
      - 1995/96, 1996 NCAA Tournament Guide (Box 55-A)
      - 1996/97, 1997 NIT Tournament Guide (Box 55-A)
      - 1997/98, 1998 NCAA and Big Ten Tournament Guides (Box 55-A)
      - 1998/99 (Box 55-A)
      - 1999/00, 2000 Big Ten Tournament Guide (Box 55-A)
      - 2000/01, 2001 Big Ten Tournament Guide (Box 55-A)
      - 2001/02 (Box 55-A)
      - 2001/02, 2002 Big Ten Tournament Guides (Box 55-B)
      - 2002/03, 2003 Big Ten Tournament Guide (Box 55-B)
      - 2003/04 (Box 55-B)
      - 2003/04, 2004 Big Ten Tournament Guides (Box 55-B)
      - 2003/04, 2004 NIT Tournament Guides (Box 55-B)
      - 2004/05, 2005 Big Ten Tournament Guide (Box 55-B)
      - 2005/06 Yearbook (Box 124-A)
      - 2005/06 Big Ten Tournament Guides (Box 124-A)
      - 2005/06 NIT Tournament Guides (Box 124-A)
      - 2008/09 (Box 124-A)
    - Miscellaneous Publications
      - Basketball Prospectus 1985/86-1989/90, 1994/95, 1999/00-2002/03 (Box 124-A)
      - Recruiting Brochures 1968, 1980, 1983, 1985, 1987, 1989, 1990 (Box 124-A)
      - Basketball Coaching Clinic Program circa 1970 (Box 124-A)
      - Michigan NCAA Championship Brackets 1948-1995 (Box 124-A)
    - Photographs
      - Team Photographs
        (also see appendix A for listing of team photos in other collections)
        - 1918, 1945, 1961, 1962, 1963, 1975 (Box 6)
        - 1918, 1921, 1926, 1927, 1929, 1944, 1945, 1948 (Box 27)
        - 1952-1953, 1955, 1957, 1958, 1961, 1964, 1966-1969 (Box 27)
        - 1970-1978, 1980, 1983, 1985-1988 (Box 27)
      - Team Photographs (Negatives)
        - 1969/70 (Box 27)
        - 1971/72 (Box 27)
        - 1972/73 (Box 27)
        - 1975/76 (Box 27)
        - 1976/77 (Box 27)
        - 1977/78 (Box 27)
        - 1978/79 (Box 27)
      - Portraits and Action Photos (see also box 6 outsize)
        - Coaches' Portraits (Box 27)
          (E.D. Mitchell, Ed Mather, George Veenker, Frank Cappon, Bennie Oosterbaan, Ozzie Cowles, Ernie McCoy, Bill Perigo, Dave Strack, John Orr, Bill Frieder, Steve Fisher, Brian Ellerbe, Tommy Amaker)
        - 1926-1927 (Box 27)
          (see photo scrapbook in outsize box 9)
        - 1925-1929 (Box 27)
          (neg. of coach Mather in Yost Arena, na 824)
        - 1930-1939 (Box 27)
        - 1940-1949 (Box 27)
        - 1948/49 trip to the west coast (Box 27)
        - 1950-1955 (Box 27)
        - 1956-1960 (Box 27)
          (see U of M News & Information Services NIS) record group, Series B, Boxes 1-2, for game action negs. & contact prints)
        - 1961-1963 (Box 27)
          (see NIS Series B, Boxes 7-10 for negs. & contact prints)
        - 1964-1966 (Box 27)
          (see NIS, Series B, boxes 10-11 and Series C, boxes 4 & 6, for negs. & contact prints)
        - 1966/67 (Box 27)
          (see NIS Series C, Boxes 7, 9-10 for negs. & contact prints)
        - Cazzie Russell photos (Box 81-B)
          (prints mounted on board)
        - 1967/68 (Box 27)
          (see NIS, Series C, Boxes 10 & 12 for negs. & contact prints)
        - 1968/69 (Box 27)
        - 1969/70 (Box 27)
          (prints, headshots, posed action, game action)
        - 1969/70 (Box 27)
          (negs. & cs, headshots, posed action)
        - 1969/70 (Box 27)
          (negs. & cs, game action)
        - Rudy Tomjanovich (Box 27)
        - 1970/71 (Box 27)
          (prints & cs, headshots, posed action, game action)
        - 1971/72 (Box 27)
          (prints, headshots, game action)
        - 1971/72 (Box 27)
          (negs, & cs, headshots)
        - 1972/73 (Box 27)
          (prints, headshots, posed action)
        - 1972/73 (Box 27)
        - 1972/73 (Box 27)
          (cs, game action)
        - 1972/73 (Box 27)
          (cs, game action, "Mayas photos")
        - 1973/74 (Box 27)
          (prints & cs, headshots, posed action)
        - 1974/75 (Box 27)
          (prints, headshots)
        - 1975/76 (Box 27)
          (prints & cs, headshots; cs of team and group shots)
        - 1975/76 (Box 27)
        - 1976/77 (Box 27)
          (Ricky Green only)
        - 1977/78 (Box 27)
          (print of Cornell Williams only)
        - 1978/79 (Box 27)
          (negs. & cs, headshots)
        - 1978/79 (Box 27)
          (cs, team & group shots)
        - 1978/79 (Box 27)
        - 1979/80 (prints, Mark Lozier only) (Box 27)
        - 1979/80 (Box 27)
        - 1980/81 (Box 27)
          (cs & color prints, headshots)
        - 1982/83 (Box 28)
          (cs & prints, headshots)
        - 1982/83 (Box 28)
        - 1982/83 (cs, individual action, Joe James) (Box 28)
        - 1982/83 (cs, individual, Ike Person) (Box 28)
        - 1983/84 (Box 28)
          (cs, headshots & team; color negs. of headshots, some posed action)
        - 1983/84 (Box 28)
        - 1983/84 (Box 28)
          (cs, individual action, Dan Pelekoudas)
        - 1984/85 (Box 28)
          (cs, headshots, team groups, coaches)
        - 1985/86 (Box 28)
          (cs, headshots & game action)
        - 1985/86 (Box 28)
          (prints, game action)
        - 1986/87 (Box 28)
          (cs, headshots and game action)
        - 1987/88 (Box 28)
          (cs, game action, Gary Grant)
        - 1988/89 (Box 28)
        - 1989/90 (Box 28)
        - 1990/91 (Box 28)
          (cs, portraits, action photos, head shots)
        - 1991/1992 (Box 28)
        - 1992 (Box 28)
          (cs, action prints and Classic draft card)
        - Chris Webber 1991-1993 (Box 28)
          (individual action)
        - 1992/93 (Box 28)
        - 1995/96 (Box 28)
          (game action slides)
        - 1996/97, 2 folders (Box 28)
          (cs, portraits, action photos, headshots, game action)
        - 1997/98 (Box 28)
          (cs, portraits, action photos, game action, headshots)
        - 1998/99, 2 folders (Box 28)
          (cs headshot, game action)
        - 1998/99 (Box 28)
          (cs, portraits, action photos, headshots)
        - 1999/2000 (Box 28)
          (cs, headshots, portraits, action photos)
        - 2000/2001 (Box 28)
        - 2001/2002, 3 folders (Box 28)
          (cs, portraits, action photos, game action)
        - 2002/2003, 2 folders (Box 28)
          (cs, game action, headshots)
        - 2002/2003 (Box 28)
          (cs, headshots and posed)
        - 2003/2004 (Box 28)
          (cs, game action, posed, prints from NIT)
        - 2000/01 (Box 28)
          (team and individual, negs.)
        - 2003/04, 2 folders game action, cs sheets and cds (Box 242)
        - 2004/05, 2 folders game action, cs sheets and cds (Box 242)
        - 2005/06, 1 folders game action, cs sheets and cds (Box 242)
        - 2005/06, 2 folders game action, cs sheets and cds (Box 243)
        - 2006/07, 3 folders game action, cs sheets and cds (Box 243)
        - Outsize action photos (Box 6)
          (including composite from 1984 NIT and 1989 NCAA Championship)
    - Game Programs
      - 1922/23 (Box 29)
      - 1949/50 (Box 29)
      - 1959/60-1963/64 (Box 29)
      - 1964/65-19667/68 (Box 29)
      - 1968/69 (Box 29)
      - 1969/70 (Box 29)
      - 1970/71 (Box 29)
      - 1971/72 (Box 29)
      - 1972/73 (Box 29)
      - 1973/74 (Box 29)
      - 1974/75 (Box 29)
      - 1975/76 (Box 29)
      - 1976/77 (Box 29)
      - 1977/78 (Box 29)
      - 1978/79 (Box 29)
      - 1979/80 (Box 29)
      - 1980/81 (Box 29)
      - 1981/82 (Box 29)
      - 1982/83 (Box 29)
      - 1983/84 (Box 30)
      - 1984/85 (Box 30)
      - 1985/86 (Box 30)
      - 1985/86 (Box 30)
      - 1986/87 (Box 30)
      - 1987/88 (Box 30)
      - 1988/89 (Box 30)
      - 1989/90, 2 folders (Box 30)
      - 1990/91 (Box 30)
      - 1992/93 (Box 30)
      - 1993/94 (Box 30)
      - 1994/95 (Box 103)
      - 1995/96 (Box 103)
      - 1996/97 (Box 103)
      - 1997/98 (Box 103)
      - 1998/99 (Box 103)
      - 2000/01 (Box 103)
      - 2001/02 (Box 103)
      - 2003/04 (Box 103)
      - 2004/05 (Box 103)
      - 2005/06 (Box 103)
      - 2006/07 (Box 103)
    - Box Scores
      - 1927/28 (score book) (Box 134)
      - 1958/59 (Box 134)
      - 1959/60 (Box 134)
      - 1960/61 (Box 134)
      - 1961/62, 2 folders (Box 134)
      - 1962/63 (Box 134)
      - 1963/64 (Box 134)
      - 1964/65 (Box 134)
      - 1965/66 (Box 134)
      - 1966//67 (Box 134)
      - 1967/68 (Box 134)
      - 1968/69 (Box 134)
      - 1969//70 (Box 134)
      - 1970/71 (Box 134)
      - 1971/72
        - Varsity (Box 134)
        - Freshman, 2 folders (Box 134)
      - 1972/73 (Box 134)
      - 1973/74 (Box 134)
      - 1974/75 (Box 134)
      - 1974/75 Scorebook (Box 134)
      - 1975/76 (Box 135)
      - 1976/77
        - Varsity (Box 135)
        - Varsity Reserve Statistics (Box 135)
      - 1977/78, 2 folders (Box 135)
      - 1978/79 (Box 135)
      - 1979/80 (Box 135)
      - 1980/81 (Box 135)
      - 1981/82 (Box 135)
      - 1982/83, 2 folders (Box 135)
      - 1983/84, 2 folders (Box 135)
      - 1984 National Invitation Tournament, 2 folders (Box 135)
      - 1984/85 (Box 135)
      - 1985/86 (Box 135)
      - 1986/87, 2 folders (Box 135)
      - 1987/88, 2 folders (Box 135)
      - 1988/89 (Box 136)
      - 1989 National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA) Tournament
        - First Four Rounds (Box 136)
        - Final Four (Box 136)
      - 1989/90, 2 folders (Box 136)
      - 1990/91 (Box 136)
      - 1991/92, 2 folders (Box 136)
      - 1992/93, 2 folders (Box 136)
      - 1993 National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA) Tournament (Box 136)
      - 1993/94, 2 folders (Box 136)
      - 1994/95, 2 folders (Box 136)
      - 1995/96 (Box 136)
      - 1995/96 Scorebook (Box 136)
      - 1996/97, 2 folders (Box 136)
      - 1996/97 Scorebook (Box 136)
      - 1997 National Invitation Tournament (NIT) (Box 136)
      - 1997/98, 2 folders (Box 137)
      - 1997/98 Scorebook (Box 137)
      - 1998 Big Ten Tournament (Box 137)
      - 1998 National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA) Tournament (Box 137)
      - 1998/99, 2 folders (Box 137)
      - 1998/99 Scorebook (Box 137)
      - 1999/2000, 2 folders (Box 137)
      - 1999/2000 Scorebook (Box 137)
      - 2000/01, 3 folders (Box 137)
      - 2000/01 Scorebook (Box 137)
      - 2001/02, 2 folders (Box 137)
      - 2001/02 Scorebook (Box 137)
      - 2002/03, 2 folders (Box 137)
      - 2003/04, 3 folders (Box 137)
      - 2003/04 Scorebook (Box 138)
      - 2004/05, 3 folders (Box 138)
      - 2004/05 Scorebook (Box 138)
      - 2005/06, 3 folders (Box 138)
      - 2005/06 Scorebook (Box 138)
    - Fab Five
      - Articles 1991-1994, 6 folders (Box 139)
      - Mailings 1995-1996 (Box 139)
      - Photographs 1991-1995 (Box 139)
      - Fab Four
        - Articles 1993 (Box 139)
        - Photographs circa 1993 (Box 139)
      - Juwan Howard
        - Articles
          - High School (Prep.) 1991 (Box 139)
          - University of Michigan (U-M) 1992-1994 (Box 139)
          - National Basketball Association (NBA) 1994-1996 (Box 139)
        - Photographs 1991-1995, 2 folders (Box 139)
        - VHS Tapes
          - "A Better Place" (Box 160)
            (Juwan Howard, featured in Chicago Housing Authority cable show, aired 8/14.2005)
      - Ray Jackson
        - Articles
          - University of Michigan (U-M) 1991-1995 (Box 139)
          - Continental Basketball Association (CBA) 1995-1997 (Box 139)
        - Photographs 1991-1995, 2 folders (Box 139)
      - Jimmy King
        - Articles
          - University of Michigan (U-M) 1991-1995 (Box 139)
          - National Basketball Association (NBA) 1995-1998 (Box 139)
        - Video
          - King / Jackson feature, VHS (Box 139)
        - Photographs 1991-1995, 3 folders (Box 140)
      - Jalen Rose
        - Articles
          - High School (Prep.) 1991-1992 (Box 140)
          - University of Michigan (U-M) 1992-1994, 3 folders (Box 140)
          - National Basketball Association (NBA) 1992-2005 (Box 140)
        - Photographs 1991-1994, 2 folders (Box 140)
        - Video
          - Jalen Rose Highlights, VHS (Box 140)
          - Jalen Rose / Jim Rome (Box 140)
      - Chris Webber
        - Articles
          - High School (Prep.) 1991 (Box 140)
          - University of Michigan (U-M) 1991-1995, 2 folders (Box 140)
          - National Basketball Association (NBA) 1992-1998, 2 folders (Box 140)
          - Magazines 1993-2000, 2 folders (Box 140)
        - Photographs 1991-1993, 2 folders (Box 140)
        - Videotapes
          - Chris Webber (Fox), VHS (Box 160)
          - Chris Webber (ESPN), VHS (Box 160)
          - Chris Webber/Jim Nantz 1993, VHS (Box 160)
          - Webber/Rose feature February 8, 1993, VHS (Box 160)
    - News Articles and Statistics
      - 1999/00 "Newspaper Game Stories" and "More Features and Clips" (Box 162)
      - 1999/00 "Players Feature" and Features and Columns" (Box 162)
      - 2000/01 "Non-Conference Game Stories" and "Big Ten Conference Game Stories" (Box 162)
      - 2001/02 Non-Conference Season Articles" and "Big Ten Conference Season Articles" (Box 162)
      - 2001/02 "Complete Statistic Package" (Box 162)
      - 2002/03 "Non-Conference Season Articles" and "Final Season Wrap-Up" (Box 163)
      - 2002/03 "Big Ten Conference Season Articles" (Box 163)
      - 2003/04 Preseason, Non-Conference, Big Ten Tournament, and NIT Tournament articles (Box 163)
      - 2003/04 "Big Ten Conference Season Articles" (Box 163)
      - 2004/05 "Non-Conference Articles" (Box 163)
      - 2004/05 "Big Ten Season Articles" (Box 163)
      - 2001 (Miscellaneous) (Box 265)
      - March 29, 2001-August 31, 2001 (Box 265)
      - December 1, 2001-January 31/2002 (Box 265)
      - February 1, 2002-March 21, 2002 (Box 266)
      - March 22, 2002-August 31, 2002 (Box 266)
      - September 1, 2002-November 30, 2002 (Box 266)
      - December 1, 2002-January 23, 2003 (Box 267)
      - January 24, 2003-March 1, 2003 (Box 267)
      - April 13, 2003-April 24, 2004 (Miscellaneous PR, etc.) (Box 267)
      - November 22, 2003-December 22, 2003 (Box 268)
      - February 3, 2004-March 12, 2004 (Box 268)
      - March 24, 2004-May 13, 2004 (Box 268)
      - November 1, 2004-December 1, 2004 (Box 269)
      - December 2, 2004-January 18, 2005 (Box 269)
      - January 19, 2005-February 23, 2005 (Box 269)
      - March 18, 2005-March 30, 2005 (Box 270)
      - May 3, 2005-December 1, 2005 (Box 270)
      - March 11, 2006-April 26, 2006 (Box 271)
      - May 13, 2006-August 23, 2006 (Box 271)
      - 2013 NCAA Tournament Articles March-April, 2013 (Folder 9)
    - Computer Disks
      (BPK files are used in Stat Crew Software)
      - 2001/02 (Box 161)
        - BPK Files (Box 161)
        - Photo CDs
          (game action)
          - EA Sports Midwest Allstars and Nike Elite 11/4/2001, 11/11/2001 (Box 161)
            (by Amir Gamzu)
          - Nike Elite 11/11/2001 (Box 161)
            (by UM Photo Services)
          - Oakland University 11/16/2001 (Box 161)
          - Bowling Green State University 11/28/2001 (Box 161)
          - Boston College 12/1/2001, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 161)
            (by UM Photo Services and Amir Gamzu)
          - IUPU-Fort Wayne 12/4/2001 (Box 161)
          - Duke 12/8/2001 (Box 161)
          - Purdue 1/5/2002, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 161)
          - Northwestern and Minnesota 1/16/2002, 1/19/2002, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 161)
          - Wisconsin 2/2/2002 (Box 161)
          - Illinois 2/7/2002 (Box 161)
          - Michigan State 1/20/2002 Wisconsin, 2/2/2002 Illinois, 2/7/2002 Penn State, 2/9/2002 Indiana, 2/17/2002 Ohio State, 3/2/2002 and Northwestern, 3/7/2002 (Box 161)
          - Penn State 2/9/2002 (Box 161)
          - Indiana 2/17/2002 (Box 161)
          - Ohio State 3/8/2002 (Box 161)
      - 2002/03
        - BPK Master Disk (Box 161)
      - 2003/04
        - Basketball Banquet Video DVD (Box 161)
        - Players, Coaches, & Support Staff Photographs (Box 161)
          (roster documents, team photos and head shots of men's and women's team)
        - Season Web Articles (Box 161)
      - 2004/05
        - BPK Disk (Box 161)
        - Season Files (Box 161)
          (season game notes, coach, player, and recruit bios, Glen Rice jersey retirement, and player head shot photographs)
      - 2005/06 (Box 161)
      - BPK Disk (Box 161)
    - Game Films and Tapes
      - Film
        - circa 1952-1960 (Box Spec. Loc.)
          (approx. 25 16mm films, some complete games others only parts of games, several films of Ron Kramer era games have been transferred to videotape)
        - circa 1963-1966 (Box Spec. Loc.)
          (approx. 15 16mm films from the Cazzie Russell era, some complete games, others only parts of games, most have been transferred to videotape)
        - ca. 1967- circa 1974 (Box Spec. Loc.)
          (miscellaneous highlight footage, including some clips from NCAA tournament action)
      - Videotape
        - 2004 National Invitational Tournament
          - UM vs Oregon March 30, 2005, VHS (Box 160)
          - UM vs Rutgers, April 1. 2004, VHS (Box 160)
  - Cross Country-men
    - Media Guides
      - 1976-1983, 1986-1987, 1989-1994, 1996-2006 (Box 31)
    - Photographs
      - Team Photos
        - 1971, 1972, 1974, 1976, 1981, 1984 (Box 31)
      - Portraits and Action Photos
        - Coaches (Box 31)
        - 1926-1927 (Box 31)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 31)
        - 1974-1977 (Box 31)
        - 1980-1984 (Box 31)
        - 1987-1989 (Box 31)
        - 1990-1999 (Box 31)
        - 2002 headshots and action (Box 31)
          (cs only, NIS #15309 and #15285)
        - 2003 headshots (Box 31)
          (cs only, NIS # 15593)
        - 2004 headshots, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 31)
          (one cd includes Nick Willis)
        - 2005 headshots and media guide cover, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 31)
        - 2005 Spartan Invitational, 9/16/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 31)
        - 2006 headshots and media guide, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 31)
        - 2006 action
          - Spartan Invitational 9/1/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 31)
          - EMU Invitational (M&W) 10/20/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 31)
        - 2007 media guide, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 31)
        - 2008 MXC Archive, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 31)
          (includes headshots, bios, media guide, results and press releases)
        - 2008 headshots, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 31)
        - 2008 action
          - Michigan Open 8/28/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 31)
          - Big Ten Meet 11/2/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 31)
    - Meet Programs and Results
      - 1971-1977 (Box 31)
      - 1978 (Box 31)
      - 1979 (Box 31)
      - 1980 (Box 31)
      - 1981 (Box 31)
      - 1982 (Box 31)
      - 1983 (Box 31)
      - 1984 (Box 31)
      - 1985 (Box 31)
      - 1986 (Box 31)
      - 1987 (Box 31)
      - 1988 (Box 31)
      - 1989 (Box 31)
      - 1990 (Box 31)
      - 1991 (Box 31)
      - 1992 (Box 31)
      - 1993 (Box 31)
      - 1994 (Box 31)
      - 1995 (Box 31)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 31)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 215)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 215)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 215)
      - 2000 (Box 215)
      - 2001 (Box 215)
      - 2008 (Box 215)
        (Big Ten meet program)
    - News Releases
      - 1989-1990 (Box 215)
      - 1991 (Box 215)
      - 1992 (Box 215)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 215)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 215)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 215)
      - 1997 (Box 215)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 215)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 215)
      - 2000 (Box 215)
      - 2001 (Box 215)
      - 2002-2006 General Info (Box 215)
  - Golf-men
    - Media Guides
      - 1938-1942, 1953, 1955, 1957-1967 (Box 32)
      - 1969-1972 (Box 32)
        (see minor sports media guides, box 81-A)
      - 1973-1977, 1979-1986, 1988-1990, 1992-1995 (Box 32)
      - 1996/97-1998/99 (Box 32)
      - 1999/00-200/01 (Box 32)
      - 2001/02-2002/03 (Box 32)
      - 2003/04-2004/05 (Box 32)
      - 2005/06-2006/07 (Box 32)
      - 2008/09 (Box 32)
    - Photographs
      - Team Photographs
        - 1934-1935, 1948 (Box 32)
        - 1955-1959, 1961-1969 (Box 32)